haydenjames.io 2019-11-19

# Privacy Policy - Linux Systems Analyst Blog - haydenjames.io

Please read the following to learn more about the Privacy Policy of this website. By visiting or using haydenjames.io you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy. Haydenjames.io is committed to protecting the privacy of users. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this website.

## Your Data Protection Rights Under GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation)

HaydenJames.io will use the information you provide via the newsletter subscribe form to be in touch with you and to provide updates. You can change your mind at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link in the footer of any email you receive, or by [contacting me](https://haydenjames.io/contact-me/). I will respond to all requests received from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights in accordance with applicable data protection laws. [MailChimp](https://mailchimp.com/) is used for newsletter marketing automation in accordance with their [Privacy Policy](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/) and [Terms](https://mailchimp.com/legal/terms/). [Disqus](https://disqus.com/) is used to manage blog comments in accordance with their [Privacy Policy](https://help.disqus.com/terms-and-policies/disqus-privacy-policy) and [Terms](https://help.disqus.com/terms-and-policies/terms-of-service).

## Information Privacy

When using the contact me form, this website collects the following information: _your name_ and _email address_. Any such personal information you provide, will never be released, sold, or rented.

## Credit card details

Note that the haydenjames.io website will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on haydenjames.io.

## External Sites

Haydenjames.io is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. Read the privacy policy of external web sites before disclosing any personal information.

## Cookies

A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows haydenjames.io to recognize you each time you visit this site. Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and haydenjames.io does not use cookies to collect any personal information.

 _Last update: July 1st 2018_

For questions or more information please [contact Hayden James](http://haydenjames.io/contact-me/).
